{
  "response_code": 0,
  "results": [
    {
      "category": "History",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which%20ancient%20civilization%20is%20known%20for%20the%20construction%20of%20the%20pyramids%20at%20Giza%3F",
      "correct_answer": "Ancient%20Egypt",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Ancient%20Greece",
        "Ancient%20Rome",
        "Mesopotamia"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "History",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "The%20city%20of%20Troy%2C%20which%20was%20the%20focus%20of%20the%20Trojan%20War%2C%20is%20located%20in%20which%20modern-day%20country%3F",
      "correct_answer": "Turkey",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Greece",
        "Italy",
        "Egypt"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "History",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "What%20is%20the%20name%20of%20the%20ancient%20city%20located%20in%20present-day%20Mexico%2C%20known%20for%20its%20pyramids%20and%20sophisticated%20civilization%3F",
      "correct_answer": "Teotihuacan",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Machu%20Picchu",
        "Chichen%20Itza",
        "Cuzco"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "History",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which%20ancient%20civilization%20is%20credited%20with%20the%20invention%20of%20writing%20using%20cuneiform%3F",
      "correct_answer": "Sumerians",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Mayans",
        "Aztecs",
        "Incas"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "History",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "The%20Minoan%20civilization%20was%20located%20on%20which%20island%20in%20the%20Mediterranean%20Sea%3F",
      "correct_answer": "Crete",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Cyprus",
        "Sardinia",
        "Sicily"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "History",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which%20ancient%20civilization%20is%20associated%20with%20the%20construction%20of%20the%20Great%20Wall%20of%20China%3F",
      "correct_answer": "Qin%20Dynasty",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Han%20Dynasty",
        "Ming%20Dynasty",
        "Tang%20Dynasty"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "History",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "The%20city%20of%20Babylon%20was%20known%20for%20its%20famous%20hanging%20gardens%2C%20which%20ancient%20civilization%20is%20associated%20with%20this%20city%3F",
      "correct_answer": "Mesopotamia",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Egypt",
        "Greece",
        "Rome"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "History",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which%20ancient%20civilization%20is%20associated%20with%20the%20creation%20of%20the%20Terracotta%20Army%20buried%20with%20the%20First%20Emperor%20of%20China%3F",
      "correct_answer": "Qin%20Dynasty",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Han%20Dynasty",
        "Shang%20Dynasty",
        "Tang%20Dynasty"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "History",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "The%20ancient%20city%20of%20Pompeii%20was%20destroyed%20by%20the%20eruption%20of%20which%20volcano%3F",
      "correct_answer": "Mount%20Vesuvius",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Mount%20Etna",
        "Mount%20St.%20Helens",
        "Mount%20Krakatoa"
      ]
    },
    {
      "category": "History",
      "type": "multiple",
      "difficulty": "medium",
      "question": "Which%20ancient%20civilization%20constructed%20the%20city%20of%20Machu%20Picchu%20in%20the%20Andes%20mountains%20of%20Peru%3F",
      "correct_answer": "Incas",
      "incorrect_answers": [
        "Mayans",
        "Aztecs",
        "Moche"
      ]
    }
  ]
}
